Daniel Nguyen

Software Engineer

Personal Data

Address

San Jose, CA

Phone

408-667-1910

E-mail

Danieltn91@gmail.com

Website

www.danielnguyen.xyz

Social Media

www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-nguyen-523120a2/

Language Skills

JavaScript, Swift, Java, HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, and MongoDB

Frameworks:

Bootstrap, AngularJS, Express.js, Nodejs, Nuance Speech Kit, DJI, Meteor, WordPress

Technical Tools

GitHub, Heroku, AWS, Sublime Text 3, Eclipse, Microsoft Offices, and Photoshop

Key Skills

Software Develop Responsive Design Project Management Team Management Working in Agile environment Outgoing Bachelor of Science Degree in Software Engineering and +2 years of experience in **software development**. Seeking to leverage my technical and professional expertise to grow in the new role of software engineer in your company.

Education

2014-08- Bachelor of Science degree in Software Engineering – GPA 3.4 **2017-12** San Jose State University, San Jose, CA

Relevant Coursework

Web Programing Data Structures Object-Oriented Design
Database Management Software Engineering Design Patterns
Mobile Development Software Project Human Computer
Management Interaction

Class Projects:

DroneItOut -Group Project, February 2017 - December 2017

- Built an iOS app using Swift, DJI SKD, Map Kit and Nuance Speed Kit
- Controlled a drone using voice commands
- Created waypoint for certain predefined paths

GigSearch – Group Project, February 2016 – May 2016

- Created Backlog, Spring Planning
- Worked closely with project manager and developers
- Developed a website using JavaScript, HTML, Bootstrap for font-end, Express and Nodejs for back-end

Experience

2016-05- Driver

present

Uber Technology Inc, San Francisco, CA

Provided transportation services to customers throughout the Bay area.

2013-04- Production Worker

2013-08

CTEMs Inc, Milpitas, CA

- Worked with team to apply tape to metal bar
- Tested metal bar with electricity

Activities/Rewards

2016-02-	Member, SCE (Software & Computer Engineering Society), SJSU
2017-12 2010-05	Scholastic achievement GPA 3.5-3.9, top 3 of Senior Honors, William C. Overfelt
2012.05	
2013-05-	Math Tutor, Evergreen Valley College
2014-01-	Volunteer, VIVO (Vietnamese Voluntary Foundation),
2014-06	
2010-03	Certificate of Excellence in recognition of my outstanding academic performance